Sean M. Kennedy

Chicago, IL | 312.320.7318 | sean47900@gmail.com | LinkedIn | GitHub

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

Highly motivated team player, whose previous work experience has sharpened multitasking and interpersonal skills. Creative, resourceful, and flexible in navigating unfamiliar situations or tasks. Effective working independently or in a group setting to accomplish goals.

Skills

HTML | CSS | JavaScript | Python | React | Node.js

PROJECTS

PropertEAZY (https://properteazy.netlify.com/)

A property management application that aims to streamline communication between owner and tenant.

React | Node.js | SQLite | PostgreSQL | Material UI | Express | Helmet | Morgan | Cors | Knex

- Payments made easy with Stripe Connect for rent payments
- File uploading so that contracts and photos of maintenance needs can be sent between tenant and owner
- Design is responsive to mobile, tablet, and desktop views

EDUCATION

Lambda School, Remote

2018 – 2019

Full Stack Web Development and Computer Science

Ball State University, Muncie, IN

2013 - 2017

Bachelor of Arts Degree in "Telecommunications and Emerging Media"

WORK EXPERIENCE

Markey's Rental and Staging, Merrillville, IN

2017 - Present

- Organizing and tearing down audio, video, and stage equipment
- Constructing stages for presentations
- Running camera and recording speakers of presentations

Northern Trust Bank, Chicago, IL

• Facilitated video and audio conferences with partners of the bank all over the world

2017 - 2018

- Answered hotline calls to troubleshoot problems with partners
- Scheduled and planned meetings with partners to ensure effective communication

On Campus Internship

ESPN 3 Ball State Video Boards, Muncie IN

2016 - 2017

- Facilitated both handheld and stationary cameras for televised sporting events on Ball State campus
- Organized production of setting up and tearing down all audio and visual equipment